Test 4. This is the IELTS listening test. You will hear a number of different recordings
and you will have to answer questions on what you hear. There will be time for you to read
the instructions and questions and you will have a chance to check your work. All the
recordings will be played once only. The test is in four parts. At the end of the test,
you will be given 10 minutes to transfer your answers to an answer sheet.
Now turn to part 1. Part 1. You will hear a man asking a friend for
advice on things to do in the city with a family of visitors. First, you have some time
to look at questions 1 to 6.
Now listen carefully and answer questions 1 to 6.
Before you hear the rest of the conversation, you have some time to look at questions 7 to 10.
Now listen and answer questions 7 to 10.
Now listen carefully and answer questions 7 to 10.
That is the end of part 1. You now have one minute to check your answers to part 1.
You now have one minute to check your answers to part 1.